Hello everyone, welcome to this very short video. I think it's going to be short but I wanted to tell you something. I received my first Louboutin heels and I don't know if you're into these kind of shoes.
I think there are a lot of fans of this brand and yeah I just wanted to show them to you and talk for a few minutes about them because I wasn't really a shoe fan or enthusiast or of these high class high fashion shoes until recently.
I spent a weekend at a friend's wedding and she has some Louboutins and I tried
them for a photoshoot so we took some lingerie pictures with the heels and
they looked good but I also realized okay they do feel really good and
they're really comfortable I wouldn't have thought this I was always like yeah
why should I pay so much money for these kind of shoes but I posted the lingerie
pictures on my Patreon and one of my patrons sent me these. So thanks a lot again. I'm overwhelmed
and yeah I'm going to turn it to you because I think they're really really cool. So I think
they're secondhand but they're in great condition. The trademark of Louboutin, the red sole is
almost perfect and I do like the design with the silver dots at the plateau here and the heel
and I also like the peep toe designs. I think it's one of my favorite shoe styles because
I have enough room for my toes but I'm going to try them.
so I think they look great together with the dress they're a bit too wide but it's only one
size above my normal size and I also heard that Louboutins are mostly smaller than their actual
size so I don't know I think I'll just put another sole in there and then it'll
be fine and I have to emphasize again that they're really comfortable I don't
know if it's the price or the special shoe design but I wouldn't have thought
this before and I do think they make a great figure and a great leg shape I
I don't know, again, if it's the hate of the heel or the overall design of the shoe.
But I really do like it.
Anyway, that was already it.
Just a quick update from my shoe closet, so to say.
And I hope you're having a great time.
See you around.